[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Running a mile burns approximately 100 calories (100 Kcal).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which fantasy-action film directed by Russell Mulcahy, the main character was born in the village of Glenfinnan on the shores of Loch Shiel?", "correct_answer": "Highlander", "incorrect_answers": ["Labyrinth", "Dune", "The Hitcher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The southern region of what US state is known as Little Egypt?", "correct_answer": "Illinois", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia", "Ohio", "Maryland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The only ingredients in a basic mayonnaise are oil and a whole egg.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the drama film 21, after Professor Rosa leaves, what does the team do?", "correct_answer": "Keep going", "incorrect_answers": ["Return to Cambridge, Mass", "Stay in Vegas and live there for the rest of their lives", "Apologize and make up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mike Nichols won an Academy Award for Best Director for the movie The Graduate.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1951 classic, The African Queen?", "correct_answer": "John Huston", "incorrect_answers": ["John Sturges", "Walter Huston", "Michael Curtiz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hairy man-apes seem to be everywhere. Which of these names is not used for them?", "correct_answer": "Hairyman", "incorrect_answers": ["Yowie", "Yeti", "Sasquatch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these is not a Greek Mediterranean island?", "correct_answer": "Minorca", "incorrect_answers": ["Lemnos", "Crete", "Santorini"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What first full admiral of the Navy, uttered the famous phrase, Damn the torpedoes, full speed ahead!, during the American Civil War at the Battle of Mobile Bay?", "correct_answer": "David Farragut", "incorrect_answers": ["Stephen Decatur", "Oliver Hazard Perry", "John Paul Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the famous roulette scene in Casablanca, what number does Rick advise the young Hungarian man to bet on?", "correct_answer": "22", "incorrect_answers": ["17", "11", "34"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cities is not a capital of a country in the European Union?", "correct_answer": "Zurich", "incorrect_answers": ["Warsaw", "Copenhagen", "Lisbon"]}]